So, I'm going to do is all the four basic punches together.
Jab, cross, hook, uppercut.
So, your going to get your guard up.
Were prepped , were ready to go.
Start with a jab then we go into a cross.
Then we go into a hook.
And, then to an upper cut.
Try it with a little tempo.
Good jab and cross and hook and upper.
Again, jab and cross, hook and up.
Now, when this goes pretty fast.
Again, if your doing this to music which is definitely a lot more fun.
If your doing this to music you want your feet to stomp with the music.
Jab, cross, hook, up.
Remember, to keep those feet lifting up off the ground.
You don't want them to ever stay planted.
Remember, the knees.
You don't want those to tweak.
So picking them up.
Jab, cross, hook, up.
You want to make sure were picking the feet up.
Cause again, feet planted not so good.